computerspeedoptimizer.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy « Computer Speed Optimizer

**Privacy Policy**

SHIELDAPPS IS COMMITTED TO PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
YOU MAY PROVIDE TO US WHEN USING ANY OF OUR ONLINE SERVICES AND ONLINE/OFFLINE  
SOFTWARE. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DESCRIBES HOW WE TREAT INFORMATION WE ARE EXPOSED  
TO WHEN YOU ARE USING OUR SOFTWARE.

**Information Collection**

When you install or purchase or download trial or evaluation versions, or register a ShieldApps software, we

may collect personal information including your name, address, email address, etc. for the purpose of

recording the transaction when you engage in activities on our web site or within the ShieldApps

software. When we use a payment-processing merchant we ensure that the same strict privacy criteria

are in place. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of

eighteen. We also give users the option of receiving useful product information (such as updates, alerts and

associated product offerings), via permission based emailing platform. We fully ensure your privacy

and value your trust. We will never sell, rent, lease or trade your personal information to any third party.

Likewise, your information will not be shared with a third party in any other way unless ShieldApps is

required to do so by law. ShieldApps may engage the services of a third party from time to time and may

provide certain information that includes personal information in order for the third party to perform

such services. Any third parties who provide services to ShieldApps have agreed not to disclose your

information or use it for any other purpose, and are required to implement or adopt a Privacy Policy

that is no less stringent than ShieldApps’ Privacy Policy. You may opt out of receiving emails from us

at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email.

By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to

ShieldApps collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein.

Any information that you post to a chat room, public bulletin, social networks or forum is available to all

permitted users of that site. ShieldApps cannot control, nor is it responsible for the use, disclosure, or

dissemination of such information by any third parties.

**Web Site Usage**

We may automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information when you access our online

services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors navigate our sites on an aggregate basis,

including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors, length of visits, etc.

**Software Usage**

We automatically collect standard usage information when you install our software (such as but not limited

to your operating system installation language, installed software, browser records, stored 3rd

and other information that is needed for our software to fulfill its purpose). This information helps us provide

you with our technical services as they are described in the software that you have installed.

**How Information Is Used When Collected**

We may use information collected in the following ways:

• To process, validate and verify purchases.

• To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of information provided.

• To register you as a customer.

• To open and maintain a support account for you.

• To send email notifications about new, existing, enhanced products or services.

• To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or

provide added products and services.

• To enable us to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs,

suggestions, or recommendations.

• To provide advance notice of termination of a trial period or an opportunity to extend a trial

period, or advance notice of expiration of your software license.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is

necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual

property rights), and your compliance with the applicable End User License Agreement(s) contained

within the ShieldApps software. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in

good faith, believe that the applicable law may require us to do so.

**Cookies**

We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer

upon access to our services. ShieldApps utilizes cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to

machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to

our customers or to our affiliates and/or other sales partners, prevent denial of service attacks on our

systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our

partners. All ShieldApps cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to

ShieldApps and its ad-serving service provider, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.

Our Cookies are mainly maintained to track our affiliates and/or other sales partners to ensure proper

payments for their sales and tracking activities relating to their affiliate relationship with us.

**Links**

We may offer links from our website and software to other third party websites which may be hosted

by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such

websites are not governed by this privacy policy and ShieldApps makes no representation as to their

practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy

of any website at the beginning of your visit.

**Security**

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We

maintain such safeguards to protect security of servers and your personally identifiable information.

We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, provide

customer service, or maintain your account with us.

**Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you in order to reflect our practices

and provide greater protection for your information. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted

promptly here, so please check back periodically.

**Acceptance of Terms**

By using the ShieldApps services, accessing the ShieldApps products and/or company website and/or

software sites you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection

and use that are described in this Privacy Policy.
